https://www.pb5th.com/privacy/

PRIVACY
PB5th acknowledges the expectations of its consumers with regard to privacy, privacy and security of their personal info that lives with PB5th. Keeping personal details of clients protected and utilizing it exclusively for activities associated with PB5th and avoiding any abuse thereof is a leading concern of PB5th. PB5th has actually embraced the privacy policy targeted at securing the personal details turned over and revealed by the clients [” the Policy”] This policy governs the method which PB5th gathers, utilizes, reveals, shops, protects and deals with personal info and delicate personal information or details.
Meanings
“Personal details” implies any info that connects to a natural individual, which either straight or indirectly, in mix with other info readily available or most likely to be offered with PB5th, can recognizing such individual
“Sensitive personal information or info” of an individual suggests such personal info which includes info connecting to:password;
monetary info such as Bank account or credit card or debit card or other payment instrument information;
physical, physiological and psychological health condition;
sexual preference;
medical records & history;
biometric info;
any information connecting to the above provisions as offered to body business for supplying service;
any of the info gotten under above provisions by body business for processing, kept or processed under legal agreement or otherwise.
Supplied that, any info that is easily offered or available in public domain or provided under the right to info act, 2005 or other law for the time being in force will not be considered as delicate personal information or info for the functions of this policy.
Applicability
This Policy applies to personal details and delicate personal information or info gathered by PB5th or its affiliates straight from the consumer or through PB5th online websites, mobile apps and electronic interactions as likewise any details gathered by PB5th server from the consumer’s web browser.
Function of Collection and Use of Personal Information
PB5th gathers and utilizes the monetary details and other personal details from its clients. This info is gathered and used for particular business functions or for other associated functions designated by PB5th  or for a legal function to adhere to the relevant laws and policies. PB5th will not disclose any personal info gathered from the client, for cross selling or other functions.
The credibility of the personal info supplied by the consumer will not be the obligation of PB5th.
Any info that is easily readily available or available in public domain or provided under the Right to Information Act, 2005 or other law for the time being in force will not be considered personal details for the functions of this Policy and PB5th will not be accountable for the very same.
Disclosure of Personal Information
The personal info gathered by PB5th  will not be revealed to other company other than:
where the disclosure has actually been concurred in a composed agreement or otherwise in between PB5th  and the consumer;
where the disclosure has actually been concurred in a composed agreement or otherwise in between PB5th and the consumer;
where PB5th is needed to divulge the personal details to a 3rd party on a need-to-know basis, supplied that in such case Sunsoft-Games will notify such 3rd party of the personal nature of the personal details and will keep the very same requirements of details/ information security as that of PB5th.
Sensible Security Practices and Procedures
The security of personal details is a top priority and is safeguarded by preserving physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that satisfy suitable laws. PB5th will take sensible actions and steps to secure the security of the consumer’s personal details from abuse and loss, un-authorized gain access to, adjustment or disclosure. PB5th preserves its security systems to guarantee that the personal info of the consumer is properly secured and follows the extant basic file encryption standards followed for the transmission of info. PB5th guarantees that its staff members and affiliates appreciate the privacy of any personal info held by PB5th.
Contact Information
In order to attend to any inconsistencies or complaints connected to the personal details living with PB5th, the client might go to: Our Website
Notification of modification
PB5th may, from time to time, alter this Policy. The reliable date of this Policy, as specified listed below, suggests the last time this Policy was modified or materially altered.
Cookie policy
PB5th digital platforms use different 3rd party analytical tools. These tools use cookies which are downloaded to your gadget when you go to a site in order to supply a customized surfing experience. Cookies are used for great deals of jobs like remembering your choices & settings, offer customized searching experience and examine website operations. These cookies gather info about how users use a site, for example, how frequently gone to pages. All info gathered by 3rd party cookies is aggregated and confidential. Using our site user/s concur that these kinds of cookies can be put on his/her gadget. User/s is totally free to disable/delete these cookies by altering his/her gadget/ internet browser settings. Sunsoft-Games is not accountable for cookies put in the gadget of user/s by other site and info gathered thereto.
©  2020 Player Bonus. Built using WordPress and the Highlight Theme
This website uses cookies to improve your experience. We'll assume you're ok with this, but you can opt-out if you wish. Cookie settingsACCEPTPrivacy & Cookies Policy
Close
Privacy Overview
This website uses cookies to improve your experience while you navigate through the website. Out of these cookies, the cookies that are categorized as necessary are stored on your browser as they are essential for the working of basic functionalities of the website. We also use third-party cookies that help us analyze and understand how you use this website. These cookies will be stored in your browser only with your consent. You also have the option to opt-out of these cookies. But opting out of some of these cookies may have an effect on your browsing experience.
Necessary
Necessary
Always Enabled
Necessary cookies are absolutely essential for the website to function properly. This category only includes cookies that ensures basic functionalities and security features of the website. These cookies do not store any personal information.
Non-necessary
Non-necessary
Any cookies that may not be particularly necessary for the website to function and is used specifically to collect user personal data via analytics, ads, other embedded contents are termed as non-necessary cookies. It is mandatory to procure user consent prior to running these cookies on your website.
